{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Italian7.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [
                "sei d'accordo?",
                "Sei d'accordo?"
            ],
            "answer": "Sei d'accordo",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1517432896.0793495,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Do you agree?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "essere d'accordo",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517432888.6256974,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to agree\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "le ragazze hanno fame"
            ],
            "answer": "Le bambine hanno fame.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517432786.5283065,
            "question": "Given the definition \"The girls are hungry.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "gli zii"
            ],
            "answer": "lo zio, gli zii",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517432853.6370795,
            "question": "zio -> (the) -> (the plural)",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "essere in orario",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1517432915.2732384,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be on time\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "essere in ritardo",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517432861.11307,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be late\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "il professore e' sempre puntuale",
                "Il professore e' sempre puntuale"
            ],
            "answer": "Il professore e' sempre puntuale.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517432872.039476,
            "question": "Given the definition \"The professor is always on time.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ho fretta"
            ],
            "answer": "Ho fretta.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517432843.5815933,
            "question": "Given the definition \"I am in a hurry.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "io sono di Roma, e' lei?"
            ],
            "answer": "Io sono di Roma, e Lei?",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517433148.095811,
            "question": "Given the definition \"I am from Rome, and you? (formal)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "lei e' d'accordo"
            ],
            "answer": "Lei e' d'accordo?",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517432962.0626435,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Do you (formal) agree?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'armadio, gli armadi",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517433166.420492,
            "question": "armadio -> (the) -> (the plural)",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "il padre e' di Venezia",
                "il padre e' di venezia"
            ],
            "answer": "Il padre e' di Venezia.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517433186.2643716,
            "question": "Given the definition \"The father is from Venice.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "gli amici sono in soggiorno"
            ],
            "answer": "Gli amici sono in soggiorno.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517433220.3914878,
            "question": "Given the definition \"The friends are in the living room.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sono",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517433065.3345058,
            "question": "Tu sei a casa. -> Io ___ casa.",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to be on time",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517432950.140091,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"essere in orario\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "in bagno c'e uno specchio"
            ],
            "answer": "In bagno c'e' uno speccio.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517433209.5592525,
            "question": "Given the definition \"In the bathrrom there is a mirror.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "lo specchio, gli specchi",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517433284.2570121,
            "question": "specchio -> (the) -> (the plural)",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "i libri sono sul tavolo",
                "I libri sono sul tavolo"
            ],
            "answer": "I libri sono sul tavolo.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517433328.865877,
            "question": "Given the definition \"The books are on the table.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "voi siete",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517433304.200198,
            "question": "Given the definition \"y'all are\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "e'",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517433319.6992755,
            "question": "(essere) Carlo ___ di Firenze.",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "essere puntuale",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517433335.1330042,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be on time\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "tu sei in ritardo"
            ],
            "answer": "Sei in ritardo.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517433316.3180957,
            "question": "Given the definition \"You (informal) are late.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Do you agree? (formal)"
            ],
            "answer": "Do you (formal) agree?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433299.7390573,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Lei e' d'accordo?\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "e'",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433257.5958605,
            "question": "(essere) La madre ___ di Roma.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sono",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433363.9705713,
            "question": "(essere) Le ragazze ___ di Roma.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il padre, i padri",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433340.919026,
            "question": "padre -> (the) -> (the plural)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "The daughter is in the bedroom"
            ],
            "answer": "The daughter is in the bedroom.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433386.3048046,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"La figlia e' in camera.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il tavolo, i tavoli",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433347.965819,
            "question": "tavolo -> (the) -> (the plural)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "siamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433367.9508204,
            "question": "Lui e' a casa. -> Noi ___ a casa.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "you are"
            ],
            "answer": "you are (informal)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433352.9281,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"tu sei\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the books are on the table"
            ],
            "answer": "The books are on the table.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433359.7629461,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I libri sono sul tavolo.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "in the bathroom there is a mirror"
            ],
            "answer": "In the bathrrom there is a mirror.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433376.098142,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"In bagno c'e' uno speccio.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the chairs are in the kitchen"
            ],
            "answer": "The chairs are in the kitchen.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433400.0046477,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Le sedie sono in cucina.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "i nonni sono in camera"
            ],
            "answer": "I nonni sono in camera da letto.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433411.5186286,
            "question": "Given the definition \"The grandparents are in the bedroom.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "siete",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433392.2938845,
            "question": "Tu sei a casa. -> Voi ___ a casa.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "The grandparents are in the bedroom"
            ],
            "answer": "The grandparents are in the bedroom.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433423.3853233,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I nonni sono in camera da letto.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la studentessa, le studentesse",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433481.3335707,
            "question": "studentessa -> (the) -> (the plural)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the baby girls are hungry"
            ],
            "answer": "The girls are hungry.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433457.4914002,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Le bambine hanno fame.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "they are in the garden"
            ],
            "answer": "They are in the garden.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433463.134448,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Loro sono in giardino.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "in cucina ci sono i piatti e le tazze"
            ],
            "answer": "In cucina ci sono i piatti e le tazze.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433445.2348146,
            "question": "Given the definition \"In the kitchen there are plates and cups.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "he, she is"
            ],
            "answer": "he/she is",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433496.5706573,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"lui/lei e'\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sono",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433501.4306684,
            "question": "Io sono a casa. -> Loro ___ a casa.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "loro sono in giardino"
            ],
            "answer": "Loro sono in giardino.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433509.231116,
            "question": "Given the definition \"They are in the garden.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the father is from Venice"
            ],
            "answer": "The father is from Venice.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433489.1054165,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Il padre e' di Venezia.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the friends are in the living room"
            ],
            "answer": "The friends are in the living room.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433531.4164438,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Gli amici sono in soggiorno.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to agree",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433512.6309593,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"essere d'accordo\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il ragazzo, i ragazzi",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433539.1022065,
            "question": "ragazzo -> (the) -> (the plural)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "siamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433521.2846732,
            "question": "(essere) Noi ___ di Firenze.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "in the kitchen there are plates and cups"
            ],
            "answer": "In the kitchen there are plates and cups.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433554.4691424,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"In cucina ci sono i piatti e le tazze.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la casa, le case",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433565.846212,
            "question": "casa -> (the) -> (the plural)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "la figlia e' in camera da letto"
            ],
            "answer": "La figlia e' in camera.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433582.9257486,
            "question": "Given the definition \"The daughter is in the bedroom.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la madre, le madri",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433544.486459,
            "question": "madre -> (the) -> (the plural)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sono",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433557.6726422,
            "question": "Loro sono in cucina. -> Io ___ in cucina.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "tu sei",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433570.5778785,
            "question": "Given the definition \"you are (informal)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "siete",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433585.7253482,
            "question": "(essere) Voi ___ di Firenze.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sono",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433560.7497077,
            "question": "(essere) Io ___ di Firenze.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "e'",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433620.161617,
            "question": "Tu sei in cucina. -> Lei ___ in cucina.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "e'",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433616.9317927,
            "question": "Lui e' a casa. -> Lei ___ casa.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the professor is always on time"
            ],
            "answer": "The professor is always on time.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433592.9844882,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Il professore e' sempre puntuale.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "lo studente, gli studenti",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433607.9859643,
            "question": "studente -> (the) -> (the plural)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "siamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433595.1676257,
            "question": "Io sono in cucina. -> Noi ___ in cucina.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la ragazza, le ragazze",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433600.7893724,
            "question": "ragazza -> (the) -> (the plural)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sono",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433613.692109,
            "question": "(essere) I ragazzi ___ di Roma.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "y'all are",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433623.341868,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"voi siete\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "noi siamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433634.641468,
            "question": "Given the definition \"we are\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la zia, le zie",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433653.3298485,
            "question": "zia -> (the) -> (the plural)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "we are",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433625.5856185,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"noi siamo\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "e'",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517433694.1898696,
            "question": "(essere) La ragazza ___ di Roma.",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to be on time",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433629.1943688,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"essere puntuale\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to be late",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433644.0669792,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"essere in ritardo\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "do you agree?"
            ],
            "answer": "Do you agree?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433686.5183637,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Sei d'accordo\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "le sedie sono in cucina"
            ],
            "answer": "Le sedie sono in cucina.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517433691.408524,
            "question": "Given the definition \"The chairs are in the kitchen.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sono",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433707.5439506,
            "question": "Lei e' in cucina. -> Loro ___ in cucina.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "la camara, le camare",
                "la camera, le camere"
            ],
            "answer": "la camera, le camare",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517433809.877319,
            "question": "camera -> (the) -> (the plural)",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il bambino, i bambini",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433704.9102437,
            "question": "bambino -> (the) -> (the plural)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la cucina, le cucine",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433712.8744478,
            "question": "cucina -> (the) -> (the plural)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "you are late"
            ],
            "answer": "You (informal) are late.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433755.390176,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Sei in ritardo.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "lui/lei e'",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433697.5968912,
            "question": "Given the definition \"he/she is\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "loro sono",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433750.4611282,
            "question": "Given the definition \"they are\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I am in a hurry"
            ],
            "answer": "I am in a hurry.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433747.9045973,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Ho fretta.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "I am from Rome, and you?"
            ],
            "answer": "I am from Rome, and you? (formal)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433835.7504005,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Io sono di Roma, e Lei?\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "siete",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433826.6868796,
            "question": "Io sono in cucina. -> Voi ___ in cucina.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "io sono",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433841.1391933,
            "question": "Given the definition \"I am\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la bambina, le bambine",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433824.432357,
            "question": "bambina -> (the) -> (the plural)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "they are",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433829.118144,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"loro sono\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "I am",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517433843.764159,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"io sono\"?",
            "tried": 2
        }
    ]
}